cealagar.com 2010-05-23

# Privacy Policy | CEAll Around Blog

At **_www.cealagar.com_** we respect your privacy.  Here you will find details outlining our privacy policy.

**What we collect**  
For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes each domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).  We use this information for statistical purposes only and do not give it away to any other parties.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website contains links to other sites.  www.singingblogger.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.

**Advertising and Cookies**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

*      Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
*      Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
*      Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Public Forums**  
Our website may make event information, chat rooms, blogs, forums, message boards, reviews, and/or news groups available to its users.  Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Choice/Opt-Out/Change**  
If you would like to opt-out of any service or change/modify information you have previously provided, please feel free to contact us at admin[at]cealagar.com

**Contacting www.cealagar.com**  
If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, feel free to contact us at admin[at]cealagar.com
